All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
There, they found themselves facing the New Fishman Pirates, who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom and instigated an all-out war.
Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of the New Fishman Pirates, thwarting their plan for revenge.
Here's the Sunny!
Yeah!
I see Frankie!
He looks like he's ready to set sail!
I can't wait!
Finally time to go!
Goodbye, Fishman Island!
Madam Charlie, Luffy and his friends are setting sail now.
Oh?
Perhaps you should see them off?
Sure thing!
Wait up!
We wanna go say goodbye too!
Sorry.
But I need somebody to stay here and run the cafe.
We'll have more tourists here now that we're rid of that despicable Hordy.
So I need you girls to keep this place in tip-top shape for me, okay?
You got it, Madam Charlie.
Oh, the crystal ball?
Don't worry.
I'm through with that now.
I don't need to look into the future anymore.
After all, Fishman Island being torn apart by straw hat Luffy.
Well, that's a future I never wanted to see.
So if my prediction turned out to be incorrect this time, then nothing would make me happier.
She knows her visions are never wrong.
She must be more scared than anyone.
And it may not come true anytime soon.
It could be tomorrow, or a year from now.
So we don't know when we can stop worrying.
Look, Madam Charlie, I know you're afraid, but Luffy-chin and the others would never-
Kami.
I hope that you'll forgive me.
I shouldn't have suspected your friends.
I see that now.
So you'd like me to trust the straw hat boy then?
Um...
Uh-huh!
Here you go!
For your trip!
Swing!
Thanks, everybody!
You ready?
Oh, Luffy!
Do you really have to set sail from here immediately?
I-I hope we just met you!
Stay with us at least one more day!
No, better yet, another week!
Or a year, perhaps?
Geez, Weepy Hochi, you haven't stopped crying since the moment we met, have you?
You're right.
I'm always a crybaby.
I'm sorry, Luffy.
Whoa!
I can't believe my fantasy is finally coming true!
The beautiful mermaid princess is in tears because she can't bear to see me go!
Bye, Sanji!
Forget the new world!
I'm happy right here!
I agree!
In fact, our time with these ladies has inspired me to compose a new song!
I met my girlfriend at the mermaid cafe!
Try not to cry!
I'll always have a place in my heart for every one of you!
I like that idea.
Maybe you should stay here.
I don't want to watch you drown in your own nosebleeds.
You're just jealous because they're not begging you to stay, ugly!
Who are you calling ugly?!
Your Majesty!
Hmm?
Should you tell them or should I?
It's only a matter of time until the tomate box reaches her!
They need to know!
If Big Mom opens the box, it'll explode!
Yes, but look at them!
It's all over!
We can't go to the new world now!
Big Mom's gonna murder us the second we get there!
Maybe if we start sending her every piece of treasure we find for the rest of our lives,
she might let it slide just this way!
If we tell them they sent her a bomb, they'll lose their will to live!
Come to think of it, Minister of the Right, those explosives are ten years old!
It's possible they're no longer functional!
Oh, I admire your positivity, Your Majesty!
We do keep it rather humid in the Ryugu Palace after all!
And who really knows if Big Mom will open the box herself anyway!
Right, then let's just hope for the best!
Do I want to know what you two are whispering about?
Hmm?
Uh, what's this?
It's a log pose for the new world.
I'd like you to take it with you.
It frightened me to think that the one you'd be using had only a single needle.
Huh?
What's up, Nami?
So you got a new log pose?
Whoa!
It looks pretty cool!
But why does it have three needles?
Well, take a look at the log pose on your wrist.
Notice anything odd?
Huh?
It's still moving!
That's funny.
I thought we had stayed here long enough for it to stabilize.
Oh, no, you did.
Half a day is all you need, but that's not the issue.
For the first half of your journey, the log pose was recording the magnetic waves of each destination,
so you were able to navigate between islands that way.
However, the second half of the Grand Line won't be so easy to predict.
In addition to the currents and the weather, some of the islands tend to experience changes in their magnetic waves as well.
Huh?
In fact, some islands have waves that disappear altogether.
Then how are we supposed to find out where they are?
Well, you're sure to lose your way with only one needle.
But now, fortunately, you'll have three of them.
Okay.
So why is one of the needles moving while the other two are sitting still?
Are you sure this thing works?
Each of the needles is recording the magnetic waves from one of three different islands.
This way, you'll be able to assess multiple paths and determine which way to travel based on your instincts as a navigator.
It's likely to make the difference between life and death for you.
A skilled navigator will know which direction is safest by simply observing the slightest movement of their needles.
There are no guarantees, but there is a good rule of thumb you can follow.
Erratic movement means more danger.
Changes in magnetic waves are often caused by abnormalities on the island.
What?
That's creepy.
I'd rather not know that stuff, thank you.
I'm with you on this one.
Me too!
Why don't you go ahead and smash that thing now?
But you mustn't.
Knowing where the danger is will help you travel more safely.
Huh?
Let me see.
Ah!
No!
Luffy!
Little one's going crazy.
That must be where the party is.
I say we go there.
Oh, we're gonna die!
Excuse me, but who's the navigator around here?
I don't try to do your job, do I?
So let me do mine!
Yeah, well I'm the captain, remember?
Uh, Captain Luffy!
We like being alive, so please listen to her, okay?
Don't be afraid, Nami!
I'll protect you!
Oh, look at her!
She's so adorable!
And now for the B-Side!
I call it Wreck-Liam Boss!
Yo!
Are you ready?
Cause it's time to get this show on the road, bro!
Huh?
Then tell me how to bring this baby back up to the top!
Well, Luffy?
Right!
Let's go!
We'll miss you!
See ya!
No!
I don't know how to bring this baby back up to the top!
I'm gonna stay here and help these folks rebuild the factory.
You sure you'll be all right without a guide?
Sure!
Sure, it was fun having you around, but I think we'll be okay.
Oh sure, screw it! We don't need a guide! I mean, what's the point?
Apparently we're just gonna waltz our way into the world of suffering and death anyway!
Exactly! Why don't we all just die right now and save ourselves of trouble, huh?
Oh dear.
Goodbye! Come back someday!
He'll bet your sweet fins I will! You ladies are all I dream about!
So much for the all blue.
You've done so much to help our kingdom. We thank you.
I pray that you will arrive safely.
Thanks!
Just you wait! By next time, whoo!
We'll be way tougher!
Even tougher than the great knight Neptune!
And we'll be commanding the most powerful army under the Cephas!
Hola tido!
Sounds good!
Now, where's...
There he is!
Jinbei!
Mr.
All right, New World, here we come!
It's time to set sail!
Goodbye, Swahead!
Well, time's a-wasting!
Goodbye! Thank you!
Come back with more candy and meat sometime!
I like humans now!
Oh, and robots and raccoons, too!
I'm reindeer, but I'll let that one go.
Oh, not me?
Be careful!
Come back any time!
Come back for more takoyaki, okay?
I love you!
Every one of you!
Ready!
Challenge is too!
You did remember!
In the beginning!
No-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Majesty!
Don't be late!
Help me, wait!
Whoa!
Shirahoshi, my love!
I just wanted to say,
if I get to see you again,
then I promise you,
I won't cry,
at least not as much as now.
I hope you and I can take another stroll together, Luffy.
Oh, yeah?
You want to go back to your mom's grave again?
No, not this time.
The place I want to go is farther away.
I want to visit a real forest,
on the surface.
That's right.
You've never been out of the sea before, have you?
Sure, let's do it.
I'll take you there first chance I get.
Oh, yeah.
Promise me.
Okay, I'll thank you, Sweria.
Leave it to me.
Careful now, Luffy.
If you make a promise, we have to help you keep it.
Remember, no matter what happens,
you must never break a promise, ever.
You know what, though? Count me in.
Oh, Nami!
And me, of course.
Yeah, me too.
And me.
Me too.
Don't forget me.
We've all given our word now.
No bones about that.
We won't let you down.
Thank you.
So don't cry anymore, okay?
Right!
What?
Ha!
I don't know.
Never forget what they've done for us.
We won't, Father.
Hey, Papa!
Can you pretty please buy me a straw hat, too?
I want to be just like Luffy.
I'm sorry, buddy, but they don't sell straw hats on the seafloor.
Then go get one from up there!
I can't do that, son.
The surface is full of humans who hate our kind.
There's no telling what they'll do if I...
Huh?
What I mean is, I've heard that some humans aren't very nice, that's all.
But they're not all the same.
Some of them are heroes, like Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey, Boss Jinbei! Perfect timing!
I just overheard.
I'm going to ask a merchant to get his hands on some of those straw hats for us.
Really?
Yes, my boy.
You'd like to be a hero, wouldn't you?
Uh-huh!
I miss it already!
All those gorgeous mermaids!
Look alive, you guys!
Don't goof off!
Once we ascend, who knows what trouble we might run into.
You remember how scary it was on the way down, don't you?
Huh?
What's with the weird boxes, Frankie?
Those are hollow cubes made out of banyan.
They're going to help us float.
I can even adjust the ship's speed based on how many I throw!
Huh?
Luffy!
What's up?
Once we reach the new world...
...Shanks won't be far away.
I hope I see him soon.
In that case, I'll leave this hat to you.
It means more to me than anything else.
I want you to bring this hat back to me.
But not until you've become a great pirate.
There is one thing...
...that hurts.
I won't be around...
...to see you fulfill your dream.
That's fine.
I have faith.
You can do it.
Because you're my brother.
There is yet joy beyond your sorrows.
What's gone may be gone.
But you still have something left in this world to treasure, don't you?
Let nothing stop you from reaching the top.
By the way, I was wondering if you've ever heard the name they use for the second half of the Grand Line.
On the other side of the Red Line, at the far reaches of the ocean, is a place that few pirates or marines have ever seen.
They call it...
The New World.
The New World!
There's a new era coming.
And the people who can guide it are gathering on those seas.
They say the one who can master those waters will become king of the pilots.
Who knows what's waiting for us up there?
That's the greatest sea in the world!
Took long enough.
I'm ready for some action.
It won't be long now, Laboon.
Just one half to go.
With this new log pose, I can take us anywhere.
And wherever we go, the sunning can handle it.
Don't worry, I'll treat all your injuries!
And as long as I'm around, you'll never go hungry.
The great Usopp's got your back too!
Alright!
Let's go!
The Straw Hats depart from Fishman Island and ascend to the surface.
The journey is not a short one, however, and it is filled with sea monsters of increasingly massive size.
While Luffy tries to make dinner out of the underwater abominations, the Sunny encounters a deadly whirlpool.
Helpless against its whipping waters, the crew must hope for a miracle to survive.
On the next One Piece, to the new world, heading for the ultimate sea, I'm going to be king of the pirates!
The